Not even 12 hours ago, I made a post to tell y'all that my friend Lauren is headed out to Minneapolis and wants to bring activity kits to kids who can't leave their homes for their family's safety.
And I gave my Venmo and holy cow, guys, you all blew me away.
I truly am so grateful for all of the people, whether you gave $5 or $500. Incredible.
Now, before I work on putting these together into little activity kits, here's what I want to say.
As awful as it can feel to let yourself bear witness to the horrors and the evils of this world, when you do that, and not only do you do that, but you roll up your sleeves and jump in,
you also get to see the beauty of humanity, and it's a privilege, and I appreciate everybody.
So, I still have thousands of dollars, and if I have time tomorrow, which I'm, I don't know if I will because my kids, but if I have time tomorrow, I'm going to get more.
Or I'm going to get sunlight stimulators to send to these families, but we are never helpless.
If we feel helpless, we roll up our sleeves and we become the helpful ones.
And never be afraid to ask because people are always looking for some way to help, and I just, I just really appreciate everybody.
So, I'm probably going to give some to the bail funds that I mentioned, but also I think that we should keep this going for as long as we need to
because I know that there are other states who are going to need this, and yeah, thank you all so much.
I don't know.